趴下，趴下!
Get down! Get down!
不许动
Don't move!
联邦调查局, 不许动!
FBI! Don't move!
趴下，趴下!
Get down! Get down!
人质在哪里?人质在哪里?
Where are the hostages? Where are the hostages?
- 联邦调查局，警察！别动！ - 趴下！别动
- FBI, Police! Don't move! - Down! Stay down!
双腿交叉 双手抱头
Cross your legs! Cross your legs and put your hands in the air!
警察 不许动，不许动! 趴下，趴下!
Police! Don't move! Police! Don't move! Get down! Get down!
都不许动 警察 这边清场!
- Clear! - Police! Search warrant. Don't move!
- 警察 不许动
- Steppin' out! - Police, don't move!
警察，别动！ 现在清场！
Police, don't move! Search warrant!
联邦调查局！
FBI!
你中枪了吗?
Are you hit?
我没事.
I'm good.
他妈的！
Fuck!
前面 交给你了
Front, you're clear!
队长 怎么样？
Team leader! Status?
领队，你那边的状况?
- Front clear! - We're clear, ma'am!
已经清场，长官，正在拘捕嫌犯.
Two suspects in custody!
- 还好吧，梅瑟? - 嗯.
- You okay, Macer? - Yeah.
你确定这里有人质吗?
Why'd he shoot? There's no one here.
哇...
Whoa...
什么鬼...
What the fuck?
上帝
Jesus!
那些不是人质.
Those weren't our hostages.
不是，那是别的什么.
No. That was somethin' else.
- 梅瑟. - 嗯?
- Macer? - Yeah?
检控官想要一个报告，你想让我怎么说?
U.S. Attorney wants a statement. What do you want me to say to her?
照实说.
The truth.
看起来像是索诺拉干的
Looks like Sonora.
是的.
Yeah.
总共有多少个?
How many, total?
大厅这里有15个，后面卧室里大概有20个.
We've got 15 in this hall here, about 20 in the back bedroom.
我们甚至还没开始检查阁楼.
We haven't even checked the attic or under the crawl space.
通知国防部，我们需要他们的人过来.
Call DOJ, let 'em know what we have.
这房子是曼努埃尔·迪亚兹的吗？
This one of the houses owned by Manuel Diaz?
是他的房子，但这事扯不到他头上.
No way to connect him, but he owns it.
我的老天.
Jesus Christ.
雷吉，去外面透口气吧.
Reg, step out. It's okay.
维克斯! 需要一个断线钳！
Vickers! I need bolt cutters!
维克斯.
Vickers!
探员好像发现了什么.
PD found something.
放松。
Relax.
在凤凰城附近发现了大量尸体.
Such a heavy body count this close to Phoenix,
显而易见，毒品集团的暴力犯罪正在严重升级.
is without a doubt a major escalation for the cartels.
在美国心脏地带发生如此触目惊心的暴行，
There will be pressure in Washington to explain how such a dramatic outrage
想必会给华盛顿方面带来巨大压力.
could happen so deep inside the American heartland.
我们谈论的可能是黑帮地盘火拼的受害者，
We may be talking about the victims of a turfwar,
也可能是被绑架勒索的偷渡者.
or maybe some illegal immigrants who are tied to a ransom,
预计我们得花上数周的时间， 才能辨清这些受害者的身份…
but it will be some weeks before we have a clearer picture on who the victims...
这是怎么回事?
What's goin' on?
不知道
I have no idea.
她领导一支反绑架小组已经有三年了.
She's been leading our kidnap response team for three years.
来这之前她接受的是这方面的培训.
Put her through the grinder since she got here, and she hasn't blinked.
她在一线做事.
She's in the front line.
没人能比凯特更乐意见到那些混蛋被绳之以法.
Nobody's gonna be happier than Kate to see these guys go down.
这么说她是个“正直的小伙伴”?
So, she's a thumper.
包括今天在内她一共部署了五次搜捕行动.
Today was her fifth O.I.S.
- 结果是五个‘零蛋’. - 对于一个新手来说，这结果不算坏
5-and-0, not bad for a rookie. She never worked cases?
她这案子办得怎么样?
She never worked cases?
- 结果是五个‘零蛋’. - 对于一个新手来说，这结果不算坏
5-and-0, not bad for a rookie. She never worked cases?
她这案子办得怎么样?
She never worked cases?
从一开始就屡屡碰壁.
Been kicking doors since day one.
她这案子办得怎么样?
She never worked cases?
从一开始就屡屡碰壁.
Been kicking doors since day one.
她的那个拍档怎么样，干这行多久了?
I like her already. What about the partner? He seen any action?
她干了只有一年半.
He's only been with us 18 months.
他有什么背景?
What's his background?
名牌大学的尖子生.曾经获得去马里兰的奖学金.
He's a sharp kid. ROTC scholarship to Maryland,
还拿到了UNC的一个法律学位.（UNC:北卡罗来纳大学）
did a tour in Iraq, got his law degree from UNC.
虽说是新手，但潜质不错.
He's green, but he's good.
这支队伍里不需要律师，我要这女孩.
No lawyers on this train. Just give me the girl.
你都是照章办事没出漏子吧?
We did this by the book, right?
废话，当然了.
Come on, of course.
- 天! - 怎么了?
- Jesus. - What?
卧槽!
Oh, shit.
凯特，你能进来吗?
Would you step in here, Kate?
今天收获不小，尽管失去了两名探员.
Quite a find today, the loss of two officers notwithstanding.
是的, 长官.
Yes, sir.
关于曼努埃尔·迪亚兹和他的生意，你知道些什么?
How familiar are you with Manuel Diaz's operation?
他的“太阳绿洲”公司这八年来一直从事房地产业务.
His company, Sun Oasis, has 80 or so foreclosure properties.
他还经营着其它的合法企业.
He has other legitimate businesses.
但传闻他和某个墨西哥贩毒集团有关.
But he's rumored to be linked with one of the Mexican cartels.
迪亚兹为一个叫做索诺拉的贩毒集团做事.
Manuel Diaz works for the Sonora Cartel.
他很可能是他们在美国的高级成员之一.
He's most likely their senior member in the United States.
你知道他的兄弟吗?
What do you know about his brother?
我不知道他有一个兄弟
I wasn't aware he had one.
吉尔莫，他兄弟叫做吉尔莫.
Guillermo. His brother's name is Guillermo.
那你知道他的表兄弟之类吗?
Do you know anything about his cousin?
我也不知道，他的档案里没这些记录.
I didn't know he had one of those either. None of that is in his file.
他有个表哥，福斯托·阿拉尔孔.
His cousin is Fausto Alarcon.
我不知道这个人.
I don't know who that is.
没有人知道，他藏起来了
No one does. He's off the grid.
他是索诺拉的第三号人物.
He's number three in the Sonora Cartel.
这些不是我管的事，长官.
This is not my department, sir.
各位，正如我刚才说的.梅瑟没经办过毒品案件
Like I said, Agent Macer doesn't work narcotics.
她一直都在负责绑架案件.
She runs a kidnap response team.
你结婚了吗?
Are you married?
问我结婚了吗?
Am I married?
你有丈夫吗?
Do you have a husband?
离婚了.
Divorced.
孩子呢?
Kids?
没有.
No.
还有别的事吗?
Anything else?
没有了...谢谢，凯特，你可以在外面等一会吗.
No. Thanks, Kate. If you could wait outside, please.
- 什么情况? - 我也不知道.
- Well? - I have no clue.
- 那些家伙是谁? 你知道吗
Who are those people? You know?
- 不知道.
No idea.
非常感谢你们过来，伙计
Thanks for coming in, guys.
凯特，再进来一下.
Will you come back in, Kate?
为了打击迪亚兹背后的贩毒集团，国防部计划成立一支专案小组.
DOJ wants advisors that focus on cartels involved in pursuing Mr. Diaz.
这位是马特·格拉弗，他将担任这个小组的头儿.
This is Matt Graver. He'll be leading the team.
不再针对这些谋杀案进行调查了吗?
Isn't this Phoenix homicide now?
不, 我们打算扩大侦查范围.
No, we're expanding the scope of the investigation a bit.
如果你愿意，可以以联络员的身份加入
You'll act as a liaison.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
他们需要你这种有实战经验的人.
They need an agent with tactical experience, like you.
国务院还招募了一名熟悉毒品领域的顾问过来.
State Department is pulling an agent from the field
专门应对日趋猖獗的的毒品犯罪活动.
that specializes in responding to escalated cartel activity.
你会成为这个专案小组中的一员.
You'll be part of the team.
你到卢克空军基地去会合.
You'll meet up with them at Luke tomorrow?
明天，中午之前吧.
Day after. Early.
空军基地?
Air Force Base?
是的.我们打算去找吉尔莫.
Yeah, we're gonna go see Guillermo.
迪亚兹的兄弟?
Diaz's brother?
正是此人.
That's the one.
他在哪?
Where is he?
埃尔帕索.（埃尔帕索：德州西部城市）
He's in the El Paso area.
此行的目的是什么?
What's our objective?
去...火上浇油.
To dramatically overreact.
凯特，这个专案小组是自愿加入的.
Kate, you must volunteer for an inter-agency task force.
考虑好再回答.
Think very hard before you respond.
你愿意加入吗?
You wanna be a part of this?
我们会抓住那些要为今天这件事负责的人吗?
Do we get an opportunity at the men responsible for today?
是真正要为今天这件事负责的人，会的.
The men who were really responsible for today, yeah.
我愿意.
I'll volunteer.
爸爸.
Papa!
- 爸爸，醒醒. - 好了，好了...
爸爸快点，我们要去参加足球比赛了.
- 你要去踢球? - 是啊.
- 真的吗? - 嗯.
- 不... - 真的，今天有比赛.
好吧，这就去吧.
妈妈，爸爸要鸡蛋和咖啡，快点好吗，我们赶时间.
好的宝贝... 我在弄住了.
亚利桑那州  卢克空军基地
你对那些家伙得多留心一点.
You keep an eye on that doughy prick with the flip-flops.
我可信不过他们.
Don't trust him.
怎么了，长官？
How you doin', sir?
身份证明.
I.D.'s?
这位女士可以进去，你不行.
She's on the list, but you're not.
搞什么鬼?
Well, what's she supposed to do?
你必须在这里倒车掉头.
I need you to turn this around for me.
没事，没事.
It's fine. It's good.
回来的时候，我会打电话给你
I'll call you when we're headed back.
好吧.
All right.
- 早上好. - 早上好. 我迟到了?
- Morning. - Morning. Am I late?
没，我刚刚降落，这边走.
No, no, no. We just landed. Come on, this way.
那家伙是我的“爪牙”，亚历桑德罗.
My bird dog over there, Alejandro.
他也一起去吗?
We're taking this?
是的，他会是你的最佳拍档.
Yeah. Only the best for you.
国防部的人都是坐私人飞机到处飞的吗，长官?
DOD flies you around in private jets now?
没错，你们也可以搞一台试试.
Yeah. You guys don't have one of these?
真牛逼
Right.
机上有吃的吗?
Is there any food on this flight?
当然，后面那里有花生，想吃的话自己拿.
Some bitchin' peanuts in the back. But it's kind of a self-serve deal.
- 凯特·梅瑟.
Kate Macer.
以前去过华雷斯吗?
Have you been to Juárez before?
没有.我们要去的是埃尔帕索, 不是吗?
No, I... We're goin' to El Paso, right?
没错，管他呢，对吧.
Yeah, amazing. Okay.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
嗯，我没事.
Yeah. I'm fine.
那个，
So...
是你擅长的吗？
So, this is your specialty?
对付墨西哥贩毒集团.
The cartels in Mexico are your specialty?
是的，是的.
Yeah. Yeah.
有什么事情是我需要了解的吗?
Is there anything I should know?
你这等于是问我，一块手表是怎么工作的?
You're asking me how a watch works.
从现在起，我们得严格按照时间计划进行.
For now, just keep an eye on the time.
好吧.
Okay.
你好吗
How you doin'?
您好！ 你怎么了？
Howdy! How you been?
好了 伙计 你感觉怎样?
Good, buddy. How you feelin'?
憋尿太久，拉的时候有点痛.
Well, when I pee, it burns.
有可能是淋病哦，
Maybe it's gonorrhea.
尿液是什么颜色?
What color is it?
黄中带红.
Yellow with red specks.
这就是血了吧
Red specks or blood?
我真想让国防部的人去看看那些发生在斐济的邪恶阴谋.
I'm tryin' to get DOD to let me look into this conspiracy to sink Fiji.
- 斐济?  - 没错.
- Fiji? - Yeah.
那里有恐怖分子吗.
Leave Fiji alone, terrorists!
要是能多待一两个月，我肯定会把他们全干掉.
Exactly. I figure a month or two over there, we'll get it all worked out.
今天还有谁去?
So, who's goin' over there today?
特警的, 禁毒局的.我几乎给你拉来了一支部队，伙计.
Marshals, DEA... I pulled a team for you, Matt.
我喜欢你用“一支部队”这个词，让我热血沸腾.
Oh, man, I love it when you say "a team." It makes me all warm and fuzzy.
这些精兵强将刚从阿富汗回来.
They're a crack bunch, too. Just rotated back from Afghanistan.
那里面有什么老相识吗?
Where's everybody linkin' up?
A.I.C.（即CIA，美国中央情报局）
A.I.C.
不错，不错，不错.
Good, good, good.
接下来，墨西哥警方会在边境和你们会合.
Mexican Federal Police will meet you at the border,
一起前往当地法院提取犯人，地点在这.
and proceed with you to the courthouse, located here.
这是一次危险性极高的行动.
This is a high-level target.
在你们提取犯人或者押送犯人过境返回的过程中.
The most likely spots for an attempt will be at the exchange,
很可能会遭到袭击.
and at the border crossing on the return.
特警将会加入进来.
The Marshals will enter...
基思，凯文，能起立一下吗?
Kevin, Keith, you wanna stand up?
这两位是来自德州拉雷多的特警.
Now, the Marshals' response team is in Laredo...
我喜欢德州.
Love Texans.
在提取和押运犯人时，
...so our friends from Delta have volunteered to come along,
三角洲特种部队会全程护送你们.
and will escort the Marshals on the exchange.
在座的各位都是行家好手.
And here's the man of the hour.
你们是跟我一起去还是留在这里?
You comin' with or waitin' here?
只要你给我几杆子好枪，我很乐意陪你去那里旅个行.
We'll take the tour with you. Loan us a couple pop guns.
棒极了，那样就是全明星阵容了吧.
All right, this is turnin' into an all-star affair!
基思, 你们还需要其他帮手吗?
Keith, you want another hand on the exchange?
你们这些“小弟弟”?
You sober?
在我们到达那里的时候...
Will be by the time we get there.
如果你吓得手颤抖，我会给你一瓶酒壮壮胆.
Got a bottle in the truck in case your hands get shaky.
我知道你一向都说到做到，基思.
I know I could always count on you, Keith.
任务完成后要啥有啥.  现在，马特.
All right, we'll gear you up as soon as we're done here.
有你坐阵，我们就不用再向三角洲要人了.
Now, Matt, you can be the tip of the spear, and we don't have to rob a guy from Delta.
在转弯拐角之处需要特别留意.
Now, be careful on the turnaround.
这些地方经常会有伏击.
If the Federale's a shooter, it's gonna happen on the turnaround.
三角洲第一小组在车队最前面领航.
Delta's Team One will be the lead vehicle.
三角洲第二小组分作两队，分别护卫押运车和尾车.清楚了吗?
We can divide Team Two between the carry car and the trail vehicle. That okay?
三角洲部队, 请亮明你们的身份.
Good. Now, Delta, if you can identify yourselves,
万一遇到出事的时候，我们就能知道有哪些人躲起来了.
so everyone knows who to hide behind if shit hits the fan.
最有可能出事的地方就是当我们过境返回的时候.
The most likely spot for a hit will be at the border crossing on the return.
任何一路上跟着我们的人，任何待在屋子外面的人， 都可能是潜在的袭击者.
Anywhere along the way, anyone not in this room is a potential shooter.
直到我们顺利回到这里，事情才算完成.
The op isn't over until we get back here.
清楚了吗?
Okay?
保持警惕，小心戒备. 千万注意. 现在出发!
Be alert. Be vigilant. And be aware. Let's go.
什么？
What?
嘿!我还以为你在监狱里。
Hey! I thought you were in prison.
他们带我出去。
They took me out.
他们需要有人做这项工作
They needed somebody for this job.
为了防止他们不良的行为？
For good behavior or bad behavior?
你以前去过那里吗?
Have you ever been over there?
我曾经在华雷斯做过事.
I worked in Juárez.
帮禁毒局做事?
For the DEA?
不.
No.
那是帮谁做事?
For who?
帮墨西哥政府.
For Mexico.
我那时候是一名控方律师.
I was a prosecutor.
你不是美国人?
You're not American?
不是.
No.
那你现在帮谁做事?
Who do you work for now?
噢，派我来的地方.
I go where I'm sent.
你是哪里派来的?
Where were you sent from?
卡塔赫纳.
Cartagena.
哥伦比亚.
Colombia.
听着...
Listen...
有些东西不是你们这些美国人能够理解的.
Nothing will make sense to your American ears.
你现在还不明白我们做的事情有何意义.
And you will doubt everything that we do.
但到最后.你一定会明白的.
But in the end, you will understand.
穿上它试试，看看是否合身.
Here, try this on. See if it fits.
他是CIA吗，或者你是吗?
Is he CIA? Are you?
他只是国防部的一个顾问，和我一样.
He's a DOD advisor, just like me.
不, 他不只...
No, he's not.
只需要好好看着亚历桑德罗. 他叫你做什么，你就照做.
Just pay attention to Alejandro. If he says to do somethin', just do it.
我没有被授权来听他的命令,
I'm not authorized to follow orders from Alejandro!
尤其是在墨西哥这里!
Especially in Mexico!
那好，那你留在这吧.
Fine. Then stay here.
可你不想这样，是吧?
But you don't want to, do you?
我只想搞清楚我掺和进了什么事里头.
I just wanna know what I'm getting into.
凯特，是你自告奋勇上了这趟车.
Kate, you volunteered to get on this train because you know
你清楚自己对凤凰城的案件有心无力.你面对的是一个操蛋的糟糕局面.
you're doing nothing in Phoenix. You're just sweeping up a fucking mess.
这6个月来，你冒死冲进每一所藏有炸弹的房子.
In six months, every single house you raid will be rigged with explosives.
不就是想抓住那些要对此负责的混蛋吗, “是”还是“不是”?
Do you want to find the guys responsible? Yes or no?
是.
Yes.
- 是!- 是?
- Yes? - Yes!
这就是我们现在开始要做的事.
This is where we start.
穿上它试试.
Try it on.
这里就是
There she is.
野兽之城
The beast.
华雷斯.
Juárez.
知道吗...
You know,
有一次，塔夫特总统去访问迪亚斯总统.
1900s, President Taft went to visit President Díaz.
带了4000个人去保护.
Took 4,000 men with him.
几乎把能带的人都带上了.
And it almost was called off.
有个家伙拿着把枪。
Some guy had a pistol.
直接走过去一枪打爆了他的头.
Was gonna walk right up to Taft and just blow his brains out.
这根本没用.4000个人.
But it was avoided. 4,000 troops!
你认为他觉得够安全了没?
Think he felt safe?
欢迎来到华雷斯.
Welcome to Juárez.
手法不错吧，他们干的这些.
It's brilliant what they do.
当他们把尸体肢解成那样..
When they mutilate a body like that,
就会让人们意识到那些死人肯定惹上不该惹的事.
they make people think they must have been involved,
才会落得如此可怕的下场.
they must have deserved such a death 'cause they did something.
这招的确不错.
It's brilliant what they do.
听见吗?
You hear that?
那可不是放鞭炮.
Those aren't firecrackers.
墨西哥人说那边有个行动，
Mexicans are adjusting our route.
我们得绕路走.大家坚持住.
There's activity ahead, we need to go around. Everyone hold on.
这里不会有事.
Nothing will happen here.
如果他们想搞事，会在边境搞.
They try anything, it will be at the border.
盯紧点这些警察.
Keep an eye out for the State Police.
他们可不一定全是好人.
They're not always the good guys.
发现可疑车辆，左边.
Spotter vehicle, left lane. Left lane!
发现可疑车辆，九点钟方向
Spotter vehicle, nine o'clock.
这些家伙真是脑子进水了.
I'm gettin' a boner.
那是我们的人？
Is that one of ours?
留意右边，留意右边
Watch the right, watch the right.
对方只是一匹独狼
No, that's a lone wolf.
留意屋顶.
Eyes on rooftops.
屋顶没东西.
Nothing.
我在摄像画面里盯着
Rooftops clear.
克里克走过 通道是安全的 先生
Bridge is one klick out. Road is secure. Hotfoot it, gentlemen.
大家都待好了. 边境的探员已经做好交接准备.
Everyone stay in this lane. Our agents at the border are
我们通过挥手 来传递信息 我想他们可以的
waving traffic through to get us over as quickly as they can.
大家保持冷静.
Everyone stay frosty.
好吧，他妈的，这下该怎么办
Okay, it's a fuck-up. What are we gonna do now?
我看到了，前方有车辆抛锚，他们正在解决.
Here's the deal. A car broke down up ahead.
需要花上点时间，全员待命.
It's being sorted out, but it's gonna take a while. Stand by.
拿好你的枪.
Get your service weapon out.
10点钟方向，两个车道以外，红色雪佛兰Impala.
Red Impala, two lanes over, on my ten.
收到，红色雪佛兰Impala，两个车道以外，左边.
Copy that. Red Impala, two lanes left.
收到.
Roger that.
左边，7点钟方向，绿色本田Civci.
Three lanes left. Seven o'clock. Green Civic.
把车窗打开.
Bring your window down.
枪.
Gun.
枪，左边
Gun! Gun left!
这里的规则是怎样?
What are the rules here?
如果他们轻举妄动，我们立刻还击.
We must be engaged to engage.
授予你们下车...和掩护射击的权限.
Permission to get out of the vehicle and set a perimeter?
先待在车里.
Stay in your vehicle.
他们下车，你们才下车.
You can do what they do. If they get out, you get out.
准做好准备.不要让他发现我们
Get ready. They can see our lane clearing.
他出来了 出来了
If it's coming, it's coming now.
行动
Move!
等等，等等..
Wait, wait, wait!
待在车里
Get outta the car.
老天.
Jesus Christ!
别动，再动的话就开枪.
别动!
Don't move!
别别别...
No, no, no, no!
伙计，伙计.
放下武器!
放下!.
嘿朋友! 问你个问题.
你想找死吗?
我们他妈的在干什么?
What the fuck are we doing?
操!
Fuck!
我们清场了.
Lane's clear! The lane's clear!
别看我!
Don't look at me!
双手抱头 快点 双手包头
Put your hands behind your head! Go! Hands behind your head!
- 清场! - 这烂摊子我来搞定!
- All clear! - I got this!
走走走
Go, go, go!
走了
Move, move, move!
这事儿肯定会登上所有美国报纸的头条.
This is gonna be on the front page of every newspaper in America.
你错了，这种事连埃尔帕索的报纸都登不上.
No, it won't. It won't even make the papers in El Paso.
知道
Clear!
有点儿疯狂，是吧?
Got a little nutty, huh?
疯狂? 是的!该死的，那是不合法的!
Nutty? Yeah, that was fucking illegal.
你是要打仗吗? 你就是个狗日的，
You wanna start a war? You're a fucking spook!
他也是. 我的意思是 那些他妈的是谁?
And him! I mean, who the fuck is that?
你可以待在这.
Told you, you could stay here.
我要疯了! 那里到处都是平民.
Jesus Christ. You just spray bullets at...
是的 当然是平民 他妈的到处都是平民
Yeah, sure, there's just fucking civilians everywhere.
我不是一个士兵，这不是我该做的.
I'm not a soldier! This is not what I do!
别这么玻璃心，行吗?
Whoa! Don't sell yourself short, all right?
雷吉不在这里，是因为我知道他还没准备好面对这个.
The reason Reggie's home is I know he wasn't ready for this.
但他最好早点做好准备，因为将来也要这样, 凯特.
But he better get ready real quick because this is the future, Kate!
在华雷斯，如果有人胡作非为他们的下场就是这样.
Juárez is what happens when they dig in. This is it!
我他妈的来这里干什么?
What am I doing here?
你来这里，就是要帮我们制造一个混乱局面.
What you're doing here is you're giving us the opportunity
制造混乱 就是这么回事!
to shake the tree and create chaos. That's what this is!
你要像海绵一样吸收你所看到的任何东西.
In the meantime, just sponge everything up you see.
学习! 这就是为什么你要来这里.
Learn! That's why you're here.
吉尔莫.
Guillermo...
你把他灌了一肚子水吗? 你真邪恶.
You're giving him a belly full of water, you devil.
你没想过会被我们抓住吧?
You didn't think we'd get you here, did you?
我不懂说英语.
No hablo Inglés.
不懂说英语?
No hablo Inglés?
那就太坏了. 我喜欢他们说 "我不懂"，杰西.
I love it when they no hablo Inglés.
知道吗，我把你的一个老朋友带来了.
You know, I brought an old buddy of yours.
我敢打赌，你一定懂怎么和他“说话”.
I bet you hablo to him. Yeah.
我不知道原来“幽灵”也会口渴.
I didn't know ghosts got thirsty.
我只知道某个人还活着.
I know someone kept him alive for us.
这种日子可不容易啊.
I doubt it was easy.
这种日子有哪天是容易的呢?
What's easy these days?
对于你所发生的事我很抱歉.
I'm sorry about what happened on the return.
不是我能控制的
I control only what I can.
是吗? 这不是你的过错.
It's not your fault.
- 你妻子怎样? - 她很好.
- 我们有两个儿子. 一个10岁，一个8岁.
- 在华雷斯? - 不，在蒙特雷.
那还好点.
嗯，那里治安更好些.
没错.
我听说这里有条隧道.
There's rumors of a tunnel.
连通亚利桑那州.
Fausto's main road into Arizona.
假如..你现在要做的事，是我想的那样...那就是最理想的途径.
If you're doing what I think you're doing, that's the best place to cross.
如果你能找到的话. 不过得尽快，时间不等人.
If you can find it. But time is against you.
机不可失，失不再来.
In three days, nobody will be where they are today.
我们该...?
Shall we?
不，你最好别进去.待会那里面会发生些事情.
No, it's better if you don't. Something happens in that room,
不用我提醒，你没有看到任何事情.
it's easier to say you didn't see anything.
很欣慰看到你仍在坚持战斗.
对于发生的事，我真的抱歉.
多保重.
亚历桑德罗，我觉得他肯定记得你.
Well, Alejandro, I think he remembers you.
我先出去.
I'm gonna step out.
蒂米。
Timmy.
再过一会，你就会明白...
“上帝的爱在美国”是什么意思了.
不...
你一直看着我也没用.
What do you keep lookin' at me for?
“我不懂说英语”，你忘了吗?
No hablo Inglés, remember?
没有
No, no.
给我根烟行吗?
Can I have one of those?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 喜欢看烟火吗? - 呃?
- You like fireworks? - Huh?
想看些有趣的玩意吗?
Wanna see something cool?
过来.
Come on.
开始了。
Here we go.
看右边那里.
Look right there.
真不敢相信.
Unbelievable.
毒贩各自为政，纷争不息.
That's what happens when you chop the head off a chicken.
嗯.
Yeah.
我看到了.
I can see.
你把他们都集中起来了?
Can you get 'em all in one place?
我刚在凤凰城下机. 我要谈谈，不能再等了.
We just landed back in Phoenix. I'm on the clock, I can't wait.
告诉鲍勃，让他在临时区等着.
All right, look, contact Bob Fisks. Have him hold 'em in the staging area.
从这里到图森要多久?
How long does it take to get to Tucson?
两个小时左右.
From here, it's a little over two hours.
好，我们争取两个小时之内赶到那.好的.
All right. We'll be there around 2:00. Yeah.
我们现在去图森吗?
Are we going to Tucson?
没错，你可以顺便练习怎样在飞机上睡觉.
Yeah, you gotta learn how to sleep on a plane.
我想你们会需要一辆顺风车.
They let me on the base when you need a ride, don't they?
你还好吗?
You okay?
我也没答你.
And yet I answered.
凯特，
Kate,
你还好吧?
who's that?
我现在要赶去图森.
We're goin' to Tucson.
怎么回事，马特? 为什么把车拦着不给走?
What's the deal, Matt? Why you holdin' up my transport?
别着急，鲍勃. 马上就好.
Don't worry, Bob. We'll be quick.
不着急才见鬼了, 差一点我TMD就得订8000美元的披萨才能安抚住这帮人.
How's the auditor gonna react to an $8,000 check to fuckin' Domino's Pizza?
别那么夸张，好吗? 这位是来自FBI的凯特·梅瑟，还有他的拍档
Don't be so dramatic, okay? This is Kate Macer with the FBI.
“他叫啥名字”，她就是这么叫的.
This is her partner, what's-his-name. It was her call.
瞎扯，我可没那么叫过. 能来根烟吗?
It wasn't my call. Have you got another one of those?
抽完了再过去.
Finish it before you get up there.
没问题
No problem.
嘿，凯特
Hey, Kate.
在埃尔帕索发生了什么事?
Tell me what happened in El Paso.
我们没去埃尔帕索. 我们去了墨西哥.
We weren't in El Paso. We were in Mexico.
我觉得我们不会按照规程来
I guess we're not following any procedures.
你打算怎么做?
What do you wanna do?
把那些从诺加莱斯来的人挑出来，我们想和他们谈谈.
We want to talk to the people caught around the Nogales area.
好的.那组.
Okay. That group.
这组.还有那组.
This group here. And that group.
就这样，他们留下来. 其余的可以走了.
Okay. They stay and the rest can go.
约瑟夫!
Josef!
注意!..注意!..
从诺加莱斯来的，A组，D组，E组
A组，D组，E组，留在原地.
其余的人上巴士...现在开始!
- 上巴士，动起来! - 马上!
- On buses, moving! - Now!
我们要找什么人?
What are we looking for?
好好看着.
Just keep watching.
这组的...
你们当中有谁曾经在美国待过?
请问一下.
在哪待过?
- 在亚利桑那州. - 亚利桑那?
- In Arizona. - Arizona?
- 结婚了吗? - 是的, 长官.
- 有孩子吗? - 是的.
- 他们在哪? - 奇瓦瓦市.
让我看看你的手.
- 你有纹身吗? - 没有, 长官.
没有吗?
- 还有你呢，叫什么名字? - 亚历桑德罗.
- 亚历桑德罗什么? - 亚历桑德罗·罗德里格斯.
- 你在哪待过? - 德州.
德州?
- 你呢你在哪待过? - 亚利桑那州.
- 亚利桑那? - 是的.
- Arizona -? Yes.
跟我说说.我们在做什么？
Talk to me. What are we doing?
我也无法回答你.
I don't have any answers for you.
那我们去打听一下啊.
Let's get some, then.
难道你以为我没问过他们吗?
Do you think I haven't asked these questions?
- 你觉得你能打听出点什么来?
Do you think you can do better?
- 当然.- 那你去吧.
- Yeah. - Go ahead.
马特，能和我聊会吗?
Matt, can we talk for a minute?
怎么了?
What's up?
没什么问题吧?
Everything okay?
你看起来好严肃.
You look very serious.
你对待我们的方式，让我们像瞎子一样.
There's "in the dark" and there's the way you're treating us.
我得搞清楚现在是什么情况.
I want to know the objective or I walk, period.
你可以走的，我可没叫你来这里.我只叫了她
Then go. I didn't ask you to be here. She did.
那我也走.
I walk, too.
- 你们想知道什么? - 所有这一切.
- What do you wanna know? - Everything.
- 操蛋的律师！
Fuckin' lawyers.
好吧.
All right.
吉尔莫
Guillermo
告诉我们在诺加莱斯的东边有条隧道，在萨萨比附近.
told us about a tunnel east of Nogales, near Sasabe.
现在我们要在这群人里面挑选一些熟悉那地区的移民、
Now we're tryin' to find out what areas near there migrants avoid,
或者帮派分子之类的人，帮我们打听出那条隧道.
so we can find the tunnel.
满意了吗?
That better?
吉尔莫?
And Guillermo is...
吉尔莫告诉你那是条运输毒品的隧道对吧.
Guillermo, he just told you where the drug tunnel is?
他只是告诉你的？
He just told you?
我们没有其他选择
Guillermo didn't have any other options.
如果把他带回墨西哥去指认 那他很有可能会被灭口.
We send him back across the border, he's a dead man.
现在他还可以在美国监狱里多活30年.
Now he gets to spend the next 30 years in an American prison,
相对安全
in relative safety.
和我们讲实话，伙计.
Just tell us the truth, man.
我们打算对曼努埃尔·迪亚兹做个局，
We are gonna make enough noise
让他会被他的老板召回墨西哥去.
that Manuel Diaz is called back to Mexico to see his boss.
这就是实话.
That's the truth.
然后呢?
And then?
然后我们顺藤摸瓜找出他老板躲在哪.
And then we know where his boss is.
他叫做“刽子手福斯托·阿拉尔孔”.
His name is Fausto Alarcon El verdugo.
拜他所赐，边境上的每一天...
Every day across that border,
都有人被绑架，或者被杀害.
people are kidnapped or killed by his hand or with his blessing.
找到了他们，就好比发现了能清除病毒的疫苗.
To find him would be like discovering a vaccine.
你明白这件事的价值所在了吗?
You understand the value of that.
好吧，我们懂了. 只是不要让我们再当瞎子.
All right, we're good. Just don't keep us in the dark.
好了.
Great!
原来他们怕黑啊...
You afraid of the dark?
嘿
Hey!
你只需要..哼哼 "全垒打之日".回家去，好好睡个觉.
It's been a humdinger of a day. Go home. Get some rest.
我们会找到另一辆顺风车的.我们明天再见
We'll find our own ride. We'll see you tomorrow!
我只开了100英里
I just drove a hundred fucking miles.
这绝对是操蛋的祝福，相信我.
It's a fucking blessing, trust me.
就是他让你又抽烟了?
Got you smokin' again?
是的.
Yeah.
吉尔莫到底他妈的是谁?
Who the fuck's Guillermo?
过来吃东西，准备去上学了.
- 爸爸去哪了? - 他去上班了.
- 那他几时回来? - 不知道.
得给你一个新文胸，女人.
Gotta get you a new bra, woman.
我要的东西有一张表那么多
The list of things I need.
我是说，一个蕾丝的...
I'm just saying. Some nice lacy somethin'.
好久没人看到过我的文胸了，除了你.
It's been a while since someone's seen me in a bra, except you.
别那样看着我，我不需要你的怜悯.
Oh, God, don't look at me like that. I don't want your pity.
改天去见见伊万吗?
How was seeing Evan the other day?
不知道.
I don't know...
- 不想他? - 说点别的.
- Miss him? - Ask me something else.
我过去遇到过像马特这样的人， 对周围的人讳莫如深，守口如瓶.
I used to see guys like Matt in Iraq. Gotta be careful around these people.
CIA不应该来插手这类案子.
CIA's not supposed to work this side of the fence.
他是国防部的一个顾问
He's a DOD advisor.
你真的信吗?
You really believe that?
你需要有人看着你确保安全，我敢保证他们没有.
You need somebody watching your six, 'cause I promise you they aren't.
你知道吗...
You know,
这案子到目前为止我们触及到的只是皮毛.
we're not even scratching the surface doing what we're doing.
一切还在原地踏步.
And they are.
那你最好他妈的亮出你的真功夫.
Well, you sure picked the motherfuckers to show us.
暗号是什么?
What's the password?
“傻逼”.
Moron.
- 你们不可能通过“洛杉矶骑士”. - 坐这.
不，你们不可能.
- 但你能， - 没错，是你的话能行.
可是别指望在“土狼”那也能行. 没有女人能通过那里.
这是我们的地盘.
This is our spot.
不行..! 不行...!
No way! No, no.
你瞧，你瞧...这里是毒品区.
唯一能通过这地方的，只有“骡子”和“肉鸡”.
他们只让这些毒品运输者通过他们的隧道.
- 因此你不可能像那样通过，对吧? - 你熟悉那片地方吗?
- 我看看... 一直以来那里都是偷渡过境的最佳通道.
从这里往86号国道方向走.
- 那里有片低洼多水的地方.
能把隧道的位置指出来吗?
Are you getting this?
看这，他们把入口藏在一辆破车后面.
这里.
那条就是我们要找的路.
That's our way across.
看来吉尔莫说的是真的.
So, Guillermo was tellin' the truth?
好事将近了.
It's gonna be a good day.
凯特，你有什么朋友在凤凰城银行吗?
Hey, Kate. Got any friends at Phoenix SWAT?
有，不过他是负责债务违约这块的
Yeah, we use them in breaches all the time.
我们得找他们帮点忙.
Good, 'cause we're gonna need their help.
帮什么?
What for?
我们要让迪亚兹的钱包...狠狠的大出血.
We are gonna fuck with Manuel Diaz's wallet.
这女人在帮他洗黑钱，伙计们. 金头发，白色背包的这个.
This is our Smurf, guys. Blonde hair, white purse.
- 你知道“海姆立克急救法”吗? - 噢，知道.
- You know the Heimlich? - Oh, yeah.
她先把赃的钱让银行吞进去，再让银行把干净的钱吐出来， 就像“海姆立克急救法”...
She tries to eat that deposit receipt, you Heimlich it right out of her, hear me?
我懂了.
Copy that.
那儿，她要走了. 逮捕他们，泰格
There she goes. All right, go get 'em, tiger.
带着他们。
Take 'em.
双手放在方向盘上!
趴下!
不许动！不许动
Hold still! Hold still!
不许动!
你要电脑监控吗?
You want bank computers for evidence?
不用，只关注钱. 冻结他的所有银行账户.
No, no. Just the money. But freeze all his accounts, everything.
就是用他的狗开的户，我也要你冻结它.
Even if his dog opened an account, I want you to freeze it.
有什么发现?
Who you got?
移动式的洗黑钱者.
Got a mobile money launderer.
收起来.
Pack it up.
起来.
Come on. Come on.
你要一起来吗?
You coming?
别进银行.
No, don't go in the bank.
这案子很快就会有突破性进展.
This is something we can actually build a case on.
别进银行，凯特.
Don't go in the bank, Kate!
她现在进银行了.
There you go, and she's goin' in the bank.
这些全都是迪亚兹账户里的?
These are all Manuel Diaz's accounts?
没错. 每天现金存款，每笔9000美元.
Yeah. Cash deposits made daily in $9,000 increments.
- 所以银行方面不会报备. - 是的.
- So, it doesn't have to be reported. - That's right.
你能查出这些账户资金的来源吗?
And you can seize that?
我已经在做了. 我们要追踪所有这些电汇号码.
I already have. And I'll go through these wire transfer numbers and
并冻结他的账户.
freeze all these accounts as well.
给你.
Here you go.
- 他妈的，太狡猾了. - 怎么了?
- Damn, that's smart. - What?
这是银行授信额度，
This is a bank line of credit.
可以用来支付欠款.
See, you make payments over what you owe,
它不表现为现金流，而是表现为负的贷款余额.
and it doesn't show up as cash, it shows up as a negative loan balance.
用这种方式他们永远都不会被银行报备. 不管是IRS还是DEA，这笔钱都是看不见的.
It's never reported to anyone. IRS, DEA... This money is invisible.
他有多少钱?
How much does he have?
看吧.
Take a look.
噢，我的天.
Oh, my God.
他们刚刚看到有1700万美元.
They just seized $17 million.
- 这是个圈套, 凯特. - 什么?
- It's a bogus bust, Kate. - What?
你起诉不了他. 这些存款账户不属于任何人.
You can't prosecute it. No one controls who deposits money in an account.
几个月之后律师就会将那些钱收回.
An attorney will have that money back in a few months,
已经有很多人吃过这招的亏了.
but a lot of heads will roll before that.
但我们现在仍然可以逮捕迪亚兹，把他关起来...
But we can arrest Manuel for now. We can get him off the street.
- 我们就是要让迪亚兹回到墨西哥，这才是目的.
We gotta get Manuel called back to Mexico. That's the objective...
我们在墨西哥没有司法管辖权.
We have no jurisdiction in Mexico.
- 我们什么都没有，我们现在必须做点什么.
We have nothing. We need to do something now.
总之我们不能逮捕他.
Can't arrest him.
什么?
What?
什么时候?
When?
等会.
Wait a minute.
每天都有9000美元存进这个账户.
$9,000 is deposited into this account every day in cash,
连续5年.
for five years.
这不违法. 这是有违法嫌疑，但真的不违法.
That's not illegal. It's suspect, but it isn't illegal.
我觉得IRS会认为这是违法的.
I think the IRS might think it's illegal.
你想要做什么, 凯特?
What do you want, Kate? What would you like done here?
我想遵照正确的程序来办.
I want to follow some semblance of procedure.
那就是我想要的.一起公正公开的司法审判.
That's what I want. To build a prosecutable case.
近两年来, 我们已经对这个地区的
We prosecuted more felony drug cases in this region last year
很多宗严重毒品案件都进行了公正公开的司法审判.
than in the two previous years combined.
但你现在走在街上，可曾有感受到?
Are you feeling that on the street?
感受到哪怕一丁点我们获胜了的氛围?
You getting the vibe that we're winning?
没有.
No.
那你呢?
Do you?
我也没有，长官.
No sir, I don't.
借用马特这样的顾问.
Advisors like Matt come in, they stir the pot,
让他们挑起事端, 迫使那些罪犯作出反应.
they cause the criminals to react and make mistakes.
从而露出破绽. 这就是在这场斗争中.
That's how we build cases against the individuals
为什么我们会采取和以往不同的办案方法的原因.
that actually make a difference in this fight.
当他们紧张, 当他们不再信任他们的成员.
It's when they're nervous, when they stop trusting their crews,
当他们转移他们的赃款.
when they move their money.
所有的这些，都会给我们创造出打击他们的好机会.
These are all opportunities to strike.
这就是找马特这些人做事的目的.
And that's the purpose of people like Matt.
凯特, 这些事并非出自我个人意愿.
Kate, this isn't something that I dreamed up myself.
我并没有权利招募顾问，或者
I don't have the authority to hire advisors,
授权某人加入专案小组，
or authorize joint agency missions,
又或者让探员在空军基地乘坐飞机.
or fly agents from Air Force bases.
你明白我的处境吗?
Are you understanding me?
这一切都是由那些
These decisions are made far from here
远离这地方的当局者决定的. 而非我们.
by officials elected to office, not appointed to them.
因此如果你担心这是超出法律界限以外的行动，
So, if your fear is operating out of bounds,
我现在告诉你,不用担心.
I am telling you, you are not.
在非常地带，用非常手段.
The boundary's been moved.
清楚了吗?
Are we clear?
是的，长官.
Yes, sir.
他妈的我要喝个痛快.
I need a fucking drink.
- 想去哪?- 去哪都行.
- Where do you wanna go? - Anywhere.
我先去“放点水”.
I'm gonna go get a table.
- 我猜这一定是为了我.- 谢谢
- I guess it's on me. - Thanks.
- 要点什么? - 两杯啤酒
- What'll it be? - Two beers.
好的，马上.
Yes, immediately.
给.
give.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想抽烟.
I want a cigarette so bad.
梅瑟?
Macer?
嗯?
Yeah?
我不喜欢说这个，但我觉得...
I hate to go on about this,
你应该不用担心文胸的状况.
but I think the bra situation's the least of your problems.
好吧...
Okay...
因为你看来像坨屎.
'Cause you look like shit.
真的. 你看起来像坨屎. 组里的每个人都这么说.
You do. You look like shit. Everybody on the team's talkin' about it.
“她曾经也像选秀选手
They're like, "Kate used to be a number one draft pick.
如今看起来却像一坨屎”.
"Now look at her. She looks like fuckin' shit."
你的眉毛也画得一团糟.
Look at you. Your eyebrows are a mess.
不，它们才不!
No, they're not!
它们看起来就像毛毛虫，小野兽，请问你们吃什么?
They're like caterpillars, like wild beasts. You're losing weight...
我不吃...
I'm eating.
你打算一件T恤衫穿一个星期?
Look at you. What is it, one T-shirt a week?
每天都要搞卫生，哈哼?
At least work on your personal hygiene, huh?
你听起来就像我老妈.
You sound like my mother.
也许我就是你的老妈.
Maybe I am your mother.
我们先是搞卫生.然后再去逛超市.
First we work on personal hygiene, then we move on to the shopping.
给你买些土豆，是吗? 多吃一点
Get you some potatoes, yeah? Eat some food...
你把我带到哪里了?这里是什么地方?
Where have you taken me? What is this place?
一个酒吧.
It's a bar.
这里全是牛仔
It's full o' cowboys.
我是一个牛仔
I'm a cowboy.
你是一个乡巴佬.
You're a redneck.
我也是一个乡巴佬. 我娶了老婆.
I'm a redneck. Got a trailer. Got a wife.
你在讲什么?
What are you talking about?
我是一个叛徒, 娶了一个老婆，他是我的妹妹.
I got a trailer, I got a wife. She's my sister.
嘿 雷吉!
Hey, Reg.
- 泰德！ - 发生了什么事？
- Ted! - What's goin' on?
- 嘿! 好久不见! - 见到你真好，伙计.
- Long time. How you been? - Yeah, it's good to see you, man.
你过得怎么样?
Good to see you, too. How you been?
你们俩在嗨起，哈哼?
Gettin' your groove on, huh?
我们刚坐下，正要开始.
We're just startin'. We just got here.
你不帮我介绍一下?
All right. You gonna introduce me, man?
特德，这是凯特·梅瑟. 我的搭档.
Ted, Phoenix PD, Kate, my partner.
你好吗? 只要是泰德 就没关系
How you doin'? Just Ted, it's fine.
我看过你玩软球.
I saw you play softball once.
软球?
Softball?
她说的是那游戏，特德.
She was at the game, Ted.
游戏?
"The game?"
三振出局, 慢速投球,
Where you struck out in slow-pitch softball.
你玩得挺不错.
You played really, really well.
我先回吧台那边.
I appreciate that.
待会能请你们再喝一轮吗?
I'm gonna head back to that bar now. Can I get y'all another round?
可以，没问题.
Yeah, sure.
好的
All right.
他人不错.
Ted, he's a good guy.
我放下这玩意，马上就好.
Just give me one second, I'll be right with you.
在这里吗? 我准备好了.
All right...
等等，等等.
Just wait, wait a second...
怎么了? 你有点过分了.
What, what? Is it too much?
我需要一点时间想想.
Just wait one minute. I just need a second.
抱歉..抱歉...
All right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
嘿 凯特.
Hey, Kate?
嘿，过来，别这样.
Hey! Hey, come here, stop, stop, talk to me.
我们聊聊，好吗? 放松点.
Just talk to me. Okay? Relax. Okay? Just take it...
该死. 凯特，
Whoa, shit! Kate...
这是怎么了?别这样.
What is it? What? Stop.
停下来...停下来...
Stop. Stop.
你他妈的在做什么?
Shit, what the fuck! What did you...
- 不要...- 他妈的你要干什么
- Don't... - What the fuck are you...
该死
God damn!
你想杀了我吗? 你他妈的疯了!?
You fuckin' try to shoot me? You fuckin' crazy?
- 停下来! - 让我走.
- Stop that! - Get off me!
他妈的...
Fuck that...
该死的 凯特 你他妈的住手
Damn it, Kate! Just fucking stop!
住手
Stop!
停下来. 我操
Stop, bitch! Stop! Fuck!
他妈的停下来!
Fuckin' stop!
住手
Stop.
妈的
Fuck!
这都是你的错. 你想要这么做
This is you, you hear me? You did this. You did this.
你拿我当诱饵
You used me as bait.
是你把自己当成诱饵.
Nah, you used yourself as bait.
我告诉过你的，别走进银行.
I told you not to go in the bank.
你被他盯上了，幸好..歪打正着.
You brought him back here, though. That was smart.
是的, 让我们假装一下我是在引蛇出洞.
Yeah. Love how we're gonna pretend like I planned this.
那你的报告就按这么写吧.
Why don't you just write that in your report.
来吧. 这是个好消息.
Come on! This is good news!
很快他们就会把曼努埃尔·迪亚兹召回去.
They're gonna call Manuel back soon.
突破性进展就要来了.
Isn't that the point?
我没事，雷吉.
It's okay, Reg.
我曾经觉得他是个朋友.
I thought he was a friend.
我知道.
I know.
- 你想我今晚留下来吗? - 不.我很好
- Want me to stay tonight? - No. I'm good.
- 确定? - 我确定
- You sure? - I'm good.
你想我告诉你, 可你他妈的一直在揍我.
How y'all want me to talk to you when you keep fuckin' hittin' me?
还有多少像你这样狗日的警界败类被边境对面那些人收买了?
How many other corrupt motherfuckers are you workin' with on this side of the border?
好吧...我...听好了.
All right. Look...
听着, 就像我说的那样.
It's exactly what I told you, all right?
他们找上我，让我在这边帮点忙.
They came to me and they wanted details about our case,
我答应了, 那是因为我不想有人因此受到伤害.
and yes, I did it, I gave it to them, but I never wanted anybody to get hurt.
我再也不会去趟这趟浑水了.
I would have never gotten involved with them pieces of shit
如果为认为有任何...
if I thought that there was any...
噢...操...好吧...好吧!
Fuck! Okay! Fuck! Okay!
好了，这些不是我们想知道的，特德.
"Okay, okay, okay," is not what we're lookin' for, Ted.
尽管你被揍了个狗血淋头，你仍然帅得一逼.
You know what the beauty is of you being so beat to a pulp?
你知道吗，没人会介意你多了几道小抓痕.
'Cause no one's gonna notice a few more scratches.
这里有笔新交易, 特德.
This is a new deal, Ted.
我可以决定你的女儿是否能够获得联邦保护.
I'm the one who decides whether your daughter'll get Federal protection,
他妈的
Fuck...
也可以决定把你前妻的地址放到网上.
or whether we post your ex-wife's address on the Internet.
我还可以决定，你是被送进一个像密苏里战争营那样的牢房,
I decide whether you go to prison in a work camp in Missouri,
还是一个“杀戮小屋”.
or a kill house like Corcoran.
好的
All right.
何去何从，取决于你，我的朋友.
This is where you negotiate how to survive, my friend.
好吧.你瞧...
Okay. Look...
我想要摆脱这一切.
I feel like this whole thing's just gotten away from me...
却搞砸了. 现在我真是头都大了.
I fucked up. Okay, I fucked up and I'm in over my fuckin' head right now.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry...
该死!让他住手! 该死的!
Fuck it! Get it out! Get it the fuck out!
让他住手! 让他住手! 该死的!
Fuck! Get it the fuck out! Get it out!
你这混蛋! 操你妈的!
Motherfucker! And fuck you!
我操!
Fuck!
还有多少官员被黑帮收买了?
How many officers do they have working on the force?
任何你想知道的我都告诉你
I'll tell you anything you wanna know.
只要你保证 我女儿的安全，好吗?
You just gotta promise me that my daughter's gonna be safe, okay?
你要向我保证.
You make me that promise.
你想听实话吗?
You want the truth?
求你了.
Please.
把所有像你这样替黑帮卖命的...
Give me all the names
...狗日的官员的名字，说出来.
of all the motherfuckers they got working on the force.
好的..好的.
Okay, okay...
- 好吗? - 好的.
- All right? - Okay...
嗯. 我们从哪个手机开始?
Okay. So, which phone do we start with?
就是那个. 最便宜的
It's in that one. That shitty one.
- 这个最便宜的 ? - 是的.
- That's the shitty one? - Yes, sir!
现在感觉怎样?
How you feelin'?
好点了.
Better.
嗯. 你应该开枪射他的.
Well, you should've shot him.
我不过是想和我的杀手..来一发...
I just tried to have sex with my hitman.
他并不想杀你.
Nah. He's no assassin.
他只是想试探，你知道了多少.
He just wanted to know what you know.
他们的矛头指向我们，不是你.
They're after us, not you.
谢谢.
Thank you.
你让我想起某个对我而言十分特别的人.
You remind me of someone very special to me.
好好睡上一觉.
Get some rest.
明天当他们返回墨西哥的时候，
Tomorrow they'll call Manuel Diaz back to Mexico,
我们会将他们连根拔起.
and we'll cut a leg from them.
确认目标. 放大图像.
We have eyes on the objective. Can we get a closer visual?
东面10米.
Ten meters going by the eastern ridge.
爸爸?
Papa?
鸡蛋.
- 辣的? - 当然.
你今天要上班吗?
晚上.
你要和我去公园踢球吗?
- 踢球? - 是的，爸爸.
- Football? - Sí, Papa.
首先得把我的咖啡拿过来.
好吧，我们去.
不.
No!
永远都不准碰它.
懂了吗?
过来吧.
Come on in.
美味的饮料？
Tasty beverage?
好啦，伙计们...
Okay, boys.
这是怎么回事? 你们计划要干什么?
What's going on? What's the plan?
我们要开始狩猎了.
We're going hunting.
曼努埃尔·迪亚兹要动身返回墨西哥了.
Looks like Manuel Diaz is being called back to Mexico.
我们正在确认.
Just waiting for confirmation.
这就是隧道，看这.
There's the tunnel right there.
好吧，听好了。
All right, listen up.
让我们理清头绪
Let's clarify the op.
我们要确定位置 继续前进
We're gonna drive to location, proceed on foot...
- 你好吗? - 很好，你呢?
- How are you? - Good. How are you?
- 我也是.- 你的脖子没事吧?
- I'm fine. - How's the neck?
好多了，谢谢.
It's better, thank you.
那就好.
Good, good.
隧道的路线图已经绘制好
These diagrams are based on other tunnels that have been mapped.
并非精确地图，仅供参考.
They're for reference only, they're not accurate.
当我们抵达边境的时候.会有一个临时落脚点
Once on the Mexican side of the border, there'll be a small staging area,
沿着画箭头的方向前往他们的毒品仓库.
then another shaft will lead to the main warehouse
事情办妥后返回墨西哥.
and the road that returns to Mexico.
那里会有很多毒品骡子吗，我们可不希望以寡敌众.
Once we clear the mules, we don't expect more than a dozen bandits.
不，他们用墨西哥警方的车来运送毒品.
No, they use Mexican police for vehicle transport.
如果你们在隧道里看到穿警服的，那肯定是跟他们一伙的.
If you see a uniform in the tunnel, consider him a bandit, too.
好的...还有其它要讨论的吗?
Okay. You want to discuss ROE?
没了，其它的迟些再说.
Nah, we'll save that for later.
好的...
Okay.
那就准备动身吧，探员们. 我们要声东击西
This is an in and out. We're clearing, placing an agent.
我们攻其不备打他们个措手不及.
It's all about creating a diversion.
我需要制造一个“大声音”.
Want the mother of all diversions, boys.
像国庆节狂欢的声音那么大.
Need a lot of noise. Fourth of July on steroids.
好了，检查好你们的武器. 来吧，伙计们.
All right. Weapons check. Let's go, boys.
目标已经确认.
This looks like confirmation.
- 我们得盯紧这辆车. - 没错，必须的.
- I need to fit your guy with a locator. - Yeah, do it.
这方面我们可是专家，我们会搞定的.
Those are Special Ops. Are we going in on this?
你们还没有装备吧.
Nah. You guys aren't really dressed for it.
为什么你不告诉我们
You didn't fuckin' tell us.
昨天你们俩个哭得像死了爹似的，
Yeah, well, you two went cryin' to Daddy yesterday, and we
- 所以没告诉你们.- 给我一个突破口
- don't want Daddy to know everything. - Give me a fucking break!
我去给你们拿些别的装备.
All right, we'll get you some extra gear.
我们的装备放在车里.
We have tac gear in the car.
太棒了，那我们就抓紧时间速战速决吧.
All right. Good. You guys will hang back when we get there, okay?
为什么叫我们去?
Then why are we going?
因为如果没有其他政府机构的人随行，CIA不能在美国国内合法行动.
'Cause CIA can't operate within US borders
他们在国内没有连接点
without a domestic agency attached.
我说过你们是有用的.
I told you you'd be useful.
所以这就是我们在这里原因.
So, that's it. That's why I'm here.
是的，完全正确.
Yeah, that's it.
这就是你们在这里的原因.
That's why you're here.
如果发现毒品，记得全部没收.
Hey, we find any drugs, you guys get to confiscate 'em.
这将会是美妙的一天.
It's gonna be a big day.
我简直不敢相信.
Un-fuckin' real!
正面和背面
Front and back.
凯特，算了. 让他们自己去折腾. 他们只是在利用我们.
Kate, come on. Fuck these people, man. They've been using us from the beginning.
我们没必要跟着去.
We don't have to do this.
我必须搞清楚整件事.
I need to know what they used us for.
- 那已经无所谓了. - 有所谓！
- Doesn't matter what! - Yes, it does!
别这样. 我们离开这，让他们全都见鬼去吧.
I say we walk and make them eat this whole fucked-up operation.
不，我必须搞清楚.
No. I have to know.
目标车辆，黑色奔驰，车牌号RIN31B7.
Black Mercedes... Plate number: Romeo-India-November-
正在往东南方向行驶.
three-one-Bravo-seven. Heading south by southeast.
在哪?
Where?
知道了.
Okay.
我们得快点赶到隧道.
We gotta hit the tunnel the minute we get on the ground.
迫不及待了，哈?
Pretty exciting, huh?
目标地点在哪?
What is the target's location?
诺加莱斯南面14公里. 往西走.
14 miles south of Nogales heading west rapidly.
打开保险栓. 枪口朝下.
Keep your fuckin' safeties on, barrels pointed down.
待在后面，
Stay in the back.
别乱开枪.  清楚了吗?
Don't shoot anyone on my fuckin' team. Right?
检查装备.
Gear check?
检查热像仪.
Thermal camera check.
检查夜视镜.
Night vision goggles check.
保持打开状态.
Get those guys.
你带A队，我带B队.
Wanna take Alpha squad, I'll take B squad?
- 就按照你说的 开始吧 - 行动吧 孩子们
- You got it. Let's do it. - Let's go, boys.
50米 三点钟方向
Fifty meters. Your three o'clock, Alpha.
已接近目标.
Stand by. Getting close to objective.
A队，B队，注意. 前方12米.
Alpha, Bravo, be advised. 12 meters straight ahead.
继续前进，悄悄溜进去，直至找到仓库中心.
All right, we need to boogie and we need to do it quiet till we find the center.
注意别发出声音.
Draw the fighters to you and make some noise.
别跟着我，我能应付.
Don't follow me. I'll be fine.
攻击规则是怎样?
What are the rules of engagement?
尽情开火，我的伙计.
Weapons free, my friend. Weapons free.
尽情开火，小家伙们.
Weapons free, boys.
祝好运
Good luck.
天哪
Oh, God!
- 你还好吗? - 我没事.
- You okay? - My gun!
跟在我后面.
Leave it. Stay on my six.
快点！快点！
快来帮忙.
- 把钥匙给我. - 不行.
- 把钥匙给我! - 冷静！
把手举起来!
转过身去!
麦德林?
别动!
Freeze!
放开他.
Step away from him.
把枪放下. 放开他.
Put that down.
我是认真的 离他远点
I mean it! Move away from him right now!
不要再拿枪对着我.
Don't ever point a weapon at me again.
喘口气，然后回隧道里去.
Catch your breath. Then get back up there.
把你的手放在方向盘上!
我过去了. 你知道我的方位吗?
I am through. Do you have my location?
知道. 我在看着你. 目标在你的东北方向.
Roger, we have you. Target is east and north of you.
17号国道. 可以从56号国道往东去拦截他.
Looks like Highway 56 to 17. Will intercept him if he stays on 17.
2队 56号国道拦截
Go east on 56 off Highway 2.
收到.
Wilco.
- 你叫什么名字? - 西尔维奥.
西尔维奥，把车开上56号国道.
我有个儿子.
现在你所做的一切都是为了你的家人.
他那边怎样吗?
Is he through yet?
我们已经把GPS传送过去了.
We have joy. GPS is transmitting. Audio is transmitting.
来了场“扫荡战”啊，朋友们.
That was a clean, clean fucking op, my friend.
除掉了两个混蛋。
Except for these two assholes.
那么 你最好逃到海外 其他的不用你管
Well, you're better overseas. You don't have to babysit.
凯特在哪?
Where's Kate?
我猜是你带的路.
I thought she was with you.
我们得回去找她
We gotta go back.
他妈的！小家伙们，我们搞丢了一个人，走吧.
Shit. Boys, we're missin' one. Let's go.
嘿
Hey!
坐下，帅哥! 别多事!
Just lay back, baby. Let it happen.
够了! 停下!
Stop! Stop!
放开我
Get off me!
停下! 停下! 请别这样!
Stop moving! Stop!
停下来!
Stop it.
冷静点! 冷静点!
Just relax. Just relax.
好了吗? 坐下来.
All right? You gonna stay there?
能安静点吗?
Are you gonna stay there?
好了.
All right.
放松点了吗.
Now, you listen.
你走错了隧道.
You went up the wrong tunnel.
你看到了你不该看到的东西.
You saw things you shouldn't have seen.
麦德林是什么意思?
What is Medellín?
麦德林?
Medellín?
麦德林是指一个时刻，（麦德林：哥伦比亚贩毒集团）
Medellín refers to a time
当由他们来垄断所有毒品贸易的时候，
when one group controlled every aspect of the drug trade,
更有利于建立起一套便于我们掌控的秩序.
providing a measure of order that we could control.
减少帮派仇杀和暴力犯罪，让毒品世界安定有序.
And until somebody finds a way to convince 20% of the population
直到有朝一日不再有人吸食那些狗屎东西.
to stop snorting and smoking that shit,
秩序是我们所能祈求的最好手段.
order's the best we can hope for.
你应该看到了
And what you saw up there,
亚历桑德罗正是他们派来构建这个秩序的.
was Alejandro working toward returning that order.
亚历桑德罗他妈的在帮哥伦比亚贩毒集团做事.
Alejandro works for the fucking Colombian Cartel.
帮我们的敌人做事.
He works for the competition.
亚历桑德罗可以帮任何人做事.
Alejandro works for anyone
只要有人找他 他就会为谁做事
who will point him toward the people who made him.
我们...
Us.
他们...
Them.
只要能帮他抓住那个...
Anyone who will turn him loose.
把他妻子的头砍下来、
So, he can get the person that cut off his wife's head,
并且把他女儿扔进一桶硫酸里面的人.
and threw his daughter into a vat of acid.
是的...
Yeah.
我和他不过是互相利用.
That's what we're dealing with.
你不能那么做.
You can't do this.
你不能.
You can't.
我很确定你们这是在做黑白勾结借刀杀人的勾当.
I'm sure as shit not the person you're gonna hide it all behind.
现在，试着放轻松点
You need to just take a breath.
我他妈的要说出来.
I'm gonna fuckin' talk.
- 不，你不会的. - 我会的.
- No, you're not. - Yeah.
我要把你们的所作所为公诸于众.
I'm gonna tell everyone what you did.
你这么做可就太不明智了
That would be a major mistake.
目标在我的前方吗? 没错
Is that the target up ahead? Confirm.
黑色奔驰就在你前方60米.
Roger that. Black Mercedes, 60 meters ahead.
西尔维奥，
Silvio...
再快点.
现在，打开警灯，
你就快拦下那辆车了.
你这个混蛋!
This motherfucker...
太好了.
- 打开扬声器，叫他下车.
下车.
再叫.
从你的车里滚出来!
叫他打开外套，然后转身.
打开外套，然后转身.
你知道我是谁吗?
让他知道，他最好乖乖照办.
我操你个狗日的.
打开外套，然后转身.
- 叫他把枪扔掉. - 把枪扔掉!
你真是一个好警察，西尔维奥.
现在到你下车.
下车，西尔维奥.
你要干什么?
别过来，狗日的! 你知道我是谁吗?
- 我是一个黑帮老大! - 趴在地上! 趴在地上!
是的, 我知道你是谁.
你是个谎话连篇、
一肚子坏水的人.
现在，你该去和你的老板见个面了.
起来!
如果你敢轻举妄动，你的女儿就会被20个男人轮奸致死.
转过身来.
上车.
- 我是曼努埃尔·迪亚兹. - 我认识你.
是曼努埃尔...核对过了.
你想去他家做什么?
What happens when we get to the house?
在门口把车停下，得下车了.
You'll stop the car, I'll get out.
我惹到什么事了?
What will happen to me?
低下头.
Slow it down.
迪亚兹先生?
还有6个.
Six remain.
我们关闭通讯了.
We're going blind.
胃口不错嘛.
继续坐着，不然他会杀了我们.
这些孩子听得懂英语吗?
不.
No.
那我们用英语说.
继续吃，继续吃.
每一晚，有多少家庭因你而家破人亡.
Every night you have families killed.
而你，却在这里安享晚餐.
And yet, here you dine.
今晚会有些不同.
Tonight should be no different.
继续吃.
那些派你来这里的人
Do you think the people that sent you here
他们和我又有什么不同?
are any different?
你知道从你身上我看到了什么吗?
Who do you think we learned it from?
一个贪婪的律师.
The grieving lawyer...
你的妻子...她会为你现在这个样子感到骄傲吗?
Your wife, you think she'd be proud of what you've become?
别忘了我的女儿.
Don't forget about my daughter.
是的，你的女儿.
你我之间并不是私人恩怨.
对我来说，是.
别伤害我的儿子.
Not in front of my boys.
是时候去接受“上帝的拥抱”了.
继续，用完你的晚餐.
Go ahead and finish your meal.
我们最好别站在阳台上聊，凯特.
I would recommend not standing on balconies for a while, Kate.
坐下吧.
Sit down.
你看起来像个担惊受怕的小女孩.
You look like a little girl when you're scared.
你让我想起我那失去了的女儿.
You remind me of the daughter they took away from me.
我需要你在这张纸上面签字.
I need you to sign this piece of paper.
确认我们的行动是合法的.
It basically says that everything we did
必须要有书面文件
was done by the book.
我不能签.
I can't sign that.
签了它.
Sign it.
没事的.
It's okay.
我不能签这字.
I can't sign that.
天啊.
God!
别做愚蠢的自杀行为，凯特.
You would be committing suicide, Kate.
来吧，签了它.
Come on. Sign it.
申请把你自己调去一个小镇
You should move to a small town,
仍有法律和正义存在的小城镇.
where the rule of law still exists.
在这里你无法生存下去.
You will not survive here.
你并不是狼.
You are not a wolf.
而这里是狼群的领地，
And this is the land of wolves now.